

#### **Contact-Detailes:**



+6017-8464 650



Alomda.alslmat@gmail.com



Al Ain, Almotared

#### Languages:

Arabic: • • • • •

English: • • • • • •

#### **Soft Skills**

- 1-) Solving problems.
- 2-) time-management.
- 3-) Project Management.

# **Programming skills:**

HTML, CSS, PHP, JavaScript, Laravel, Vue.js, MYSQL , Sass , JQuery, Tailwind, liveware, Ajax , Python, AWS

## **Certifications:**

- 1-) Building Database Applications in PHP (coursera)
- 2-) HTML, CSS, and JavaScript for Web Developers ( coursera )
- 3-) Front-End Web UI Frameworks and Tools: Bootstrap 4, (coursera)
- 4-) Introduction to Structured Query Language (SQL) (coursera)
- 5-) PHP framework: laravel, codeigniter
- 6-) AWS Fundamentals (coursera)

#### **References:**

Ali A.Alwan Aljuboori Assistant Professor KULLIYYAH OF INFORMATION AND COMMUNICATION TECHNOLOGY International Islamic University Malaysia

Email: aliamer@iium.edu.m

## Summary:

Junior Web Developer specializing in front-end and back-end development. I have a good knowledge of all stages of the development cycle for dynamic web projects. Well-versed in numerous programming languages including and tools { HTML, CSS, PHP, OOP, JavaScript, Laravel, Vue.js, MYSQL, Sass, JQuery, Tailwind, liveware, Ajax, Python, AWS, git, git-hub, alpine.js }.

Live Portfolio->https://mohammadalsalamat.github.io/Portfolio/index.html

# **Experience:**

Web Developer - Free Lancer, IIUM

02/2018 to 01/2019

Building websites for the users who ask me to do so such as Student's Final year. Besides tens of other individual projects One of my works was an E-commerce

website to sell Suits built it using laravel framework.

Web Developer - Final year Project, IIUM, Malaysia

02/2019 to 09/2019

Final year project (FYP) is one of the biggest challenges that I had due the tools that I used to build teaching website where I used Codelgniter Framework to complete it in very short time, and it was my first own website using new tools such as Codelgniter,

# Internship:

### Web Developer - George HealthCare, Malaysia

02/2020 to 08/2020

It is Internship period but I got lots of experiences where I built the main admin page for the company's website and I helped them to improve lots of features to make the website more attractive to users and helped the team to build the security for the website then worked on Front-End side where I helped to build the functions to get the data from the database.

## **Education:**

International Islamic University (IIUM), Malaysia

SEP 2016 / JAN 2020

Bachelor's in information and Communication Technology,

International Islamic University Malaysia (IIUM), KL, Malaysia

## **Examples & Templates:**

Live Demo ->https://mohammadalsalamat.github.io/Mountain Travel/.

Live Demo->https://mohammadalsalamat.github.io/Grapgy/.